{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "忙" ,
      "answer": "Máng | busy"
    },
    {
      "question": "爸爸",
      "answer": "Bàba | dad"
    },
    {
      "question": "吗" ,
      "answer": "Ma | a particle used for questions expecting a yes-no answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "妈妈",
      "answer": "Māmā | mum"
    },
    {
      "question": "他们",
      "answer": "Tāmen | they, them"
    },
    {
      "question": "他",
      "answer": "Tā | he, him"
    },
    {
      "question": "们",
      "answer": "men | used after pronouns 我，你，他 or certain nouns to denote plurality"
    },
    {
      "question": "都",
      "answer": "Dōu | both, all"
    },
    {
      "question": "不",
      "answer": "Bù | not, no"
    },
    {
      "question": "男",
      "answer": "Nán | male"
    },
    {
      "question": "朋友",
      "answer": "Péngyǒu | friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "呢",
      "answer": "Ne | a modal particle used for elliptical questions"
    },
    {
      "question": "哥哥",
      "answer": "Gēgē | elder brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "要",
      "answer": "Yào | to want"
    },
    {
      "question": "咖啡",
      "answer": "Kāfēi | coffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟弟",
      "answer": "Dìdì | younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "喝",
      "answer": "Hē | to drink"
    }
  ]
}
